Mss.B.J44 Mss.B.J44
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 18, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: Norman V. Donaldson. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 28, 1933; 5-1/2x3-1/4; Yale University Press
    Typed L.S.: J.M.Weber, on postal card. 1p.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his publications.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 3, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: Norman V. Donaldson. 1p.and enc. of 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards reviews of his book.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 22, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: Irene Weber. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Glad to sell him books.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Jan. 22, 1942; 5-1/4x4; Zook, Helen Phyllis
    A.L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks question concerning the amoeba.
  - Certificate of membership to Herbert S. Jennings as corresponding member, March 18, 1936; 9x11-3/4; Zoological Society of London
    London, Printed D.filled in in type, S.: Julian S. Huxley. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Jan. 13, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Zuckerman, H G
    Los Angeles, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Sends article which he wrote.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, May 11, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Zuckerman, H G
    Berkeley, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thank you letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, July 3, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Zuckerman, H G
    Berkeley, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Lecture given at Bozeman, Montana, on Naples, 1898; 10-1/2x8; Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.
    ca. A.D. 31p. (see H.S.Jennings papers. no.1.)
  - Lectures: Genetics., 1913-1914; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Law of ancestral inheritance; A.D. 32p. (see H.S. Jennings papers. no. 10.)
  - Lectures: Genetics., 1913-1914; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Law of ancestral inheritance. Changes during longcontinued breeding; A.D. 26p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 11.)
  - Biology and the principles of human conduct, 1920; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 28p. In pencil. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 12.)
  - Lectures: Genetics., 1920; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Inheritance of acquired characteristics; A.D. 132p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 13.)
  - Biometry and the law of probabilities, 1920; 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 68 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 14.)
  - Lectures: Genetics., 1920-1921; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Pure line work; A.D. 45p. (see H.S. Jennings papers. no. 15.)
  - Lectures: Effects of selection, 1920-1921; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 66 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 16.)
  - Lectures: Method of evolution, 1920-1921; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 232 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 17.)
  - Address: On the advantages of growing old, 1921; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 81 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 18.)
  - Biometry notes, 1921; 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 55 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 19.)
  - Number of pairs drawn when individuals are taken at random, 1913; Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.
    A.D. 102 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings. Papers, no.2.)
  - The arithmetic of heredity and variation, 1922; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 147 leaves and copy of R.W. Emerson's Tables of Probable errors...and J.R. Miner's Tables... (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 20) ---Typed copy of 100 pages and carbon copy of 97 pages.
  - Concerning the lunatic fringe, 1922; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 15 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings, no. 21.)
  - Biometry notes, 1922; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 13 leaves and 1 notebook consisting of 30 leaves, of which 25 contain writing. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 22.)
  - Material pertaining to the Mendel-Pasteur centennial celebration at St. Louis, 1922; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 8 leaves, 8 newspaper items, and invitation to the celebration. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 23.)
  - Leidy's zoological work, 1923; 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 12p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 24.) ----Typed copies (3) and galley sheets as printed in Scientific monthly. Printed: Acad. of nat.sci,Phila. Proceedings, 1923; and Scientific monthly, vol.18.
  - Lectures: Population notes, April 30, 1923; 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 99p. In pencil. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 25.)
  - Notes on genetic papers, 1923; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    D. 105 leaves. Various sizes. (see H. S. Jennings papers.No.26:)
  - Biometry, 1923; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    D. 9 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 27.)
  - Reviews on protozoa, 1924; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    D. 34 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 28.)
  - Lectures: Inheritance of acquired characteristics, March, 1924; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 55 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 29.)
  - The biology of children in relation to education, 1917; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, Herbert S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    Mimeographed D. 16p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 3.)
  - Lectures: Genetics of protozoa [fragments], 1924-1925; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.and typed D. 367 leaves. Various sizes. (H.S. Jennings papers. No. 30.)
  - Lecture: Human elements in science, 1925; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 21p. In pencil. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 31.)
  - Lecture:, 1925; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 35p. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 32.)
  - Notes on Richard Hertwig's writings on genetics in protozoa, April 29, 1925; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 97 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 33.)
  - Lectures, 1925; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 16 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 34.)
  - Lecture: Adventures of the evolution idea, Nov. 11, 1925; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 76 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 35.)
  - Lecture: Determinism, Feb., 1926; 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 70 leaves. In pencil. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 36.)
  - Lecture: Unsettled and unsettling problems in science, March 11, 1926; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 71 leaves. In pencil. (see H. S. Jennings papers, no. 37.)
  - Lecture: Genetics of protozoa, 1927-1928; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 643 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 38.)
  - Report of Jollo's work, Aug., 1928; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 27p. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 39.)
  - August Weismann and W. Roux, 1917-1919?; 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer?, 1868-1947.]
    [ca.] A.D. 39p. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 4.) (Is this a translation from Radl: Later fortunes of the theory of natural selection?)
  - Lecture: Biological results of race crossing, Dec. 1, 1928; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 45 leaves. In pencil. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 40.)
  - Seminary talks: Emergent evolution, 1928; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 124 leaves. In pencil. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 41.)
  - Creation by evolution, 1928; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 28p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 42.)
  - Genetics of the protozoa (outline or resumé), 1929; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Typed D. 23p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 43.)
  - Lecture: History of zoology in America, May 13, 1929; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 86 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers. no. 44.)
  - Lecture: Genetics., 1929-1930; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Changes in hereditary characteristics; A.D.and mimeographed D. 264 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 45.)
  - Lecture: Biological background of social work (incomplete), Oct. 14, 1930; 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 18 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 46.)
  - Lecture: Identical twins, May 22, 1930; 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 16 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 47.)
  - Lecture: Can men be bettered psychologically and ethically by breeding?, Oct. 17, 1932; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 34 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 48.) ----Typed copy and carbon copy, each of 30p.
  - Lecture: Religion in the light of science, 1932-1933; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.and typed D. 59 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 49.)
  - Concerning protozoon genetics, 1919; 8-3/4x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 46 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings. No. 5.)
  - Concerning Japan, 1933 (?); 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 89 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 50.)
  - Protozoon problems, Dec. 29, May 24, 1932, 1933; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 71 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers. no. 51.)
  - Lectures: Biologists outlook on the world, 1933; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Typed D. 32p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 52.)
  - Lecture: Biologists outlook on the world (Philadelphia lecture), 1933; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 35 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers. no. 53.) Typed copy of 29 leaves.
  - Concerning twins, Feb. March, 1933, 1935; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.and typed D. 45 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 54.)
  - Lecture: Genetics., 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Changes in hereditary characteristics and in the genetic mechanism; 1933-1934. A.D. 573 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 55.)
  - Lectures: Statistics, 1933-1934; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 425 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 56.)
  - Concerning the role of the school, 1934; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 29 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 57.)
  - Lecture: Mutations, 1934-1935; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 212 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 58.)
  - Lecture: Genetic variations, 1934-1935; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 39 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 59.)
  - Concerning inheritance in pure lines, Dec. 24, 1919; 11x8-1/2, 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 54 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 6.)
  - Lecture: Genetics., 1934-1935; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Types of genetic variation in relation to evolution and to environment; A.and typed D. 11 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 60.)
  - Lecture: Genetics., 1934-1935; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Changes in chromosomes; A.D. 26 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 61.)
  - Heritable effects of conjugation between free individuals and double monsters in diverse races of paramecium caudatum, [1934]; 11x8-1/2; De Garis, Charles F
    Typed D. 76 leaves and 2 illustrations, sent to H.S. Jennings. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 62.)
  - Lecture: The universe and life, April 27, 1935; 5-1/2x4-1/4; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 49 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 63.)
  - Concerning Japan, 1935 (?); 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 106 leaves and 1 newspaper clipping (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 64.)
  - Review of Alexis Carrel's book, Man, the Unknown, 1935; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    A.D.S. 8p.and 43p.of notes. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 65.)
  - Lecture: Behavior of lower organisms, 1935; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 72 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 66.)
  - Lecture: Zoological seminary: Present day questions in biology, Jan. 16, 1935; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 24p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 67.)
  - Lecture: Zoological seminary: Indeterminism in relation to uncertainty, Feb. 6, April 10, 1935; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D.and typed D. 35 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 68.)
  - Report to the genetics conference on the crossing in paramecium, Feb., 1935; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 47 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings,papers, no. 69.)
  - Seminar reports: On the nature of science, etc., 1912-1913; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    D. 66p. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 7.)
  - Lecture on the crossing in paramecium, March 6, 1935; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 47 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 70.)
  - Resumé of The Universe and Life, 1935; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 53 leaves. (see H.S.Jennings papers. No. 71.)
  - Lecture: Concerning the role of mutation in evolution, Feb. 1, Feb. 12, 1935, 1936; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 41 leaves. Presented to the A.P.S. Feb. 1, 1935. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 72.)
  - Lecture: Biological recommendations for the ills of mankind, June 3, 1936; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Typed and A.D. 72 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 73.)
  - Fundamental units in biology, Oct. 10, 1936; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    Typed D. 17 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 74.) ----Galley proof from Science. 5p.
  - Lecture: Experiences at Oxford, Dec. 21, 1936; 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 74 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 75.)
  - Lecture: Genetics, 1936-1937; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 463 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings, papers, no. 76.)
  - Tables: Paramecium, etc., Sept., Jan., 1937-1938; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 22 items. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 77.)
  - The genetics of paramecium bursaria: mating types and groups, March, 1939; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Typed and A.D. 81 leaves and illustrations. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 78.)
  - Chromosomes and cytoplasm in protozoa, 1940; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 26p.and 83p.of notes, with 5p.of galley proof. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 79.)
  - Lectures: Sex determination in bees, moulds, plants, etc., 1914; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 58p. (see H. S. Jennings papers, no. 8.)
  - Heredity in protozoa, 1940; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Typed and A.D. 82 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 80.)
  - Hereditary status of the rhizopods, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    Typed D. 25p. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 81.)
  - The laws of heredity and our present knowledge of human genetics..., 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    A. and typed D. 157ms.leaves and 92 typed leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 82.)
  - The beginnings of social behavior in unicellular organisms, 1941; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    Typed D. 34p.and carbon, with 7p.of galley proof. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings Papers, no. 83.)
  - Genetics of paramecium, 1941; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    Typed D. 83p.with 3p.figures, also 29p. of galley proof. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 84.) Printed in APS Proceedings,vol.85.
  - The effect of natural selection in the acclimatization of Euplotes..., 1940; Gause, G[eorge] F[rancis], 1910-
    Typed D. 21p. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 85.) This manuscript was originally sent to H.S. Jennings, see letter from Gause to Jennings; Nov. 21, 1940.
  - Levels of integration in biological and social systems, 1941-1942; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    A.and typed D. 28p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 86.) ----Typed copy of 23p.and galley proof of 5p. Printed: Science, vol.94, 447-453.
  - Senesecence and death in protozoa and invertebrates, March 4, 1942; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    A.and typed D. 61p.and carbon copy. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers no. 87.)
  - Biographical memoir of Raymond Pearl, 1879-1940, 1943; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    A.D. 31 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers. No. 88.) ----Typed carbon of 27p.
  - Changes in the surrounding medium produced by free-living cells, 1943; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    A.D. 30p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 89.) ----Typed copy of 25p.with carbon of 22p.and 3p.galley proof. Printed: Colloid chemistry, pp. 1162-1174.
  - Lectures: Genetics., 1913-1914; 11x8-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Pure line work; A.D. 12p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 9.)
  - Lecture: Seminary in sociology., 1943; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    The meaning of genetics as to the nature of man; A.and typed D. 179 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 90.)
  - Genetics of paramecium bursaria from Russia, 1944; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    Typed and A.D.S.: H.S. Jennings, Tze-Tuan Chen and Pauline S. Opitz. 66 leaves, 2 illustration, and 8p. of galley proofs (2 copies). Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 91.) Printed: Genetics, v.29; Nov. 1944.
  - Paramecium bursaria: Life history, 1944; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    Typed D.and A.D. 421 leaves, 4 illustrations, and 5p.of galley proof. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 92.) Printed: Biological bulletin,vol.86.
  - Social life and interrelationships in certain protozoa, Jan. 27, 1945; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    Typed D. 18p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 93.)
  - Review of Leo Loeb's The biological basis of individuality, April 24, 1945; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    Typed D. 4p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 94.) ----Carbon copy and galley proof. Printed: Science, 98.
  - Paramecium bursaria, June, 1945; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H[erbert] S[pencer], 1868-1947.
    Typed D. 27p. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 95.) ----Carbon copy, 27p. Printed: Journal of experimental zoology; June 1945.
  - Illustrations for various articles., [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. and photographs. 108 items. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 96.)
  - Newspaper clippings made in England, 1935-1936; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    Printed items. 143p. Q. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 97.)
  - Lectures given at Indiana university, 1943; Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.
    D.and typed D. 482 leaves. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings Papers, no. 98.) Lectures on biology.
  - Miscellaneous manuscript notes, 1935; 8-1/2x5-1/2; [Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.]
    A.D. 79 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers, no. 99.)
  - Greetings from students and colleagues on his Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of his doctorate, March, 1921; 12-1/2x10; Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.
    L.S. 1vol.of ca. 110 items, many with photographs. Congratulatory letters. Presented by Burridge Jennings (son of Dr. Jennings); April 1964.
  - Letters presented on his 75th birthday, April 8, 1943; 11-1/2x10; Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947.
    L.S. lvol.of ca.200 items. Congratulatory letters. Presented by Burridge Jennings (son of Dr. Jennings); April 1964.
  - Autobiography, 1895; 9 1/4" x 8 3/4"; Jennings, George Nelson, 1833-1903.
    [with a continuation by his daughter, Helen Jennings Barrett, 1937]. A.D. 121 leaves, port. Mentions his son, Herbert S. Jennings, APS member. Presented by Miss Carolyn Jennings, his granddaughter October 1957.